const BasicCppQuestions = [
    {
      question: "What does 'C++' stand for?",
      options: ["C Plus Plus", "Central Processing Unit", "Computer Programming Language", "C Positive Positive"],
      correct_option: "C Plus Plus"
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the following is not a fundamental data type in C++?",
      options: ["int", "float", "string", "boolean"],
      correct_option: "string"
    },
    {
      question: "What symbol is used to indicate a single-line comment in C++?",
      options: ["//", "/*", "#", "--"],
      correct_option: "//"
    },
    {
      question: "Which keyword is used to define a function in C++?",
      options: ["method", "func", "define", "void"],
      correct_option: "void"
    },
    {
      question: "What is the result of 5 + 3 * 2 in C++?",
      options: ["10", "16", "26", "Error"],
      correct_option: "11"
    },
    {
      question: "Which header file is used for input and output operations in C++?",
      options: ["<inputoutput.h>", "<iostream.h>", "<io.h>", "<iostream>"],
      correct_option: "<iostream>"
    },
    {
      question: "What is the purpose of 'cin' in C++?",
      options: ["To output data", "To input data", "To define a constant", "To perform arithmetic operations"],
      correct_option: "To input data"
    },
    {
      question: "Which operator is used for dynamic memory allocation in C++?",
      options: ["new", "&", "*", "alloc"],
      correct_option: "new"
    },
    {
      question: "What is the size of 'int' data type in C++?",
      options: ["4 bytes", "2 bytes", "8 bytes", "Depends on the compiler"],
      correct_option: "4 bytes"
    },
    {
      question: "Which loop is used to execute a block of code repeatedly in C++?",
      options: ["if-else loop", "for loop", "switch loop", "do-while loop"],
      correct_option: "for loop"
    },
    {
      question: "What is the purpose of 'break' statement in C++?",
      options: ["To terminate the loop", "To skip the next iteration of the loop", "To exit the program", "To continue to the next iteration"],
      correct_option: "To terminate the loop"
    },
    {
      question: "Which function is used to find the length of a string in C++?",
      options: ["len()", "length()", "strlength()", "strlen()"],
      correct_option: "strlen()"
    },
    {
      question: "What is the default return type of a function in C++?",
      options: ["int", "void", "float", "char"],
      correct_option: "int"
    },
    {
      question: "Which operator is used to access the member functions and variables of a class object in C++?",
      options: [".", "->", "::", "{}"],
      correct_option: "->"
    },
    {
      question: "What is the purpose of 'const' keyword in C++?",
      options: ["To define a constant", "To declare a variable", "To create a class", "To specify a loop condition"],
      correct_option: "To define a constant"
    }
  ];
  
  export default BasicCppQuestions;
